vndic.org 2013-05-19

# Privacy Policy

**Personal Information**  
Anivide.com is committed to providing you with the best experience we can on our website. We gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. Your IP address is used to gather information and to track your general visiting patterns. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Anivide.com as outlined in this privacy policy. We do not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third party unless specified. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Cookies & Third Party Cookies**  
Some ads displayed may come from our servers. Ads loading from our servers may also contain cookies, the purpose of these cookies is just to introduce and select the proper advertisements to be shown for your interests. We only have access to information of visiting frequencies of our visitors from cookies you might receive while viewing ads from our servers. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Anivide.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
